<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jiang Muyun</title>
    <link>/authors/jiang-muyun/</link>
      <atom:link href="/authors/jiang-muyun/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Jiang Muyun</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/images/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>Jiang Muyun</title>
      <link>/authors/jiang-muyun/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complex Industrial Process Modeling and Monitoring with Conditional Recurrent Variational Autoencoder</title>
      <link>/publication/j-tii-crvae/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/j-tii-crvae/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    This paper is submitted and currently under review
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!-- Traditional Gaussian process regression (GPR) suffers from the cubic complexity and excessive computation burdens for industrial big data. To get rid of such defect, this work proposes a scalable soft sensor called bagging stochastic variational GP regression (BSVGPR). We first formulate the GP within the sparse and variational approximation framework. Then the stochastic variational inference (SVI) mechanism is induced, which can significantly break the formidable obstacle to nonlinear big data modeling. In addition, the imposed automatic relevance determination strategy will also leverage model interpretability with relevant feature weighting.  Based on that, the bagging mechanism is encompassed by combining a set of distributed predictors to form a powerful ensemble model. As the results, prediction accuracy is enhanced, while the stability is also well guaranteed. Both SVI and bagging allow for the parallel deployment. Therefore, a distributed diagram is developed for modeling and inference so that the BSVGPR can explore big data effectively and efficiently. For case study demonstrations, the proposed method is first evaluated on the numerical example, and then applied on the real-time oxygen prediction of hydrogen manufacturing unit. --&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intelligent Soft Sensor Development for Nonlinear Industrial Big Data via Bagging Bayesian Gaussian Processes</title>
      <link>/publication/j-tie-svgpr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/j-tie-svgpr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    This paper is submitted and currently under review
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!-- Traditional Gaussian process regression (GPR) suffers from the cubic complexity and excessive computation burdens for industrial big data. To get rid of such defect, this work proposes a scalable soft sensor called bagging stochastic variational GP regression (BSVGPR). We first formulate the GP within the sparse and variational approximation framework. Then the stochastic variational inference (SVI) mechanism is induced, which can significantly break the formidable obstacle to nonlinear big data modeling. In addition, the imposed automatic relevance determination strategy will also leverage model interpretability with relevant feature weighting.  Based on that, the bagging mechanism is encompassed by combining a set of distributed predictors to form a powerful ensemble model. As the results, prediction accuracy is enhanced, while the stability is also well guaranteed. Both SVI and bagging allow for the parallel deployment. Therefore, a distributed diagram is developed for modeling and inference so that the BSVGPR can explore big data effectively and efficiently. For case study demonstrations, the proposed method is first evaluated on the numerical example, and then applied on the real-time oxygen prediction of hydrogen manufacturing unit. --&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ShadowVLAD: Semantic attentional NetVLAD encoding and matching for Place Recognition</title>
      <link>/publication/c-cvpr-svlad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/c-cvpr-svlad/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    This paper is submitted and currently under review
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This paper addresses the problem of large-scale visual place recognition (VPR). To cope with the uneven distribution and the unequal discriminability of visual cues in an image, we provide an attention-regulated encoding paradigm named ShadowVLAD. The paradigm adopts a hierarchical weighted embedding mechanism for both attention-aware local refinement and global integration. The local refinement compounds the semantic prior and a locally double weighting scheme into an interpretable module, where local features are clustered, refined and quantified as informative visual word representations. For global integration, a weighted similarity voting kernel has been proposed to embed those heterogeneous representations into final image descriptor with varying weights. By this means, discriminative visual words play a more important role in similarity voting during indexing. All proposed modules are differentiable and can be optimized in an end-to-end manner. Even without pixel level annotations, the learnt attention turns out to be consistent with human behavior patterns. Experiments demonstrate that ShadowVLAD outperforms previous state-of-the-art techniques on city-scale VPR benchmark data sets.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Place Recognition Using Line-Junction-Line in Urban Environment</title>
      <link>/publication/c-cisram-ljl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/c-cisram-ljl/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Place recognition plays a vital role in eliminating accumulated drift from visual odometry in SLAM system. Visual place recognition has been considered a very challenging task, because traditional image key point descriptors suffers from change appearance of a place during multiple traversals. We propose a novel Line-Junction-Line (LJL) descriptor to build Bag of Word (BoW) dictionary for robust place recognition in urban environments. Line-Junction-Line is a structure of two lines with their intersection. LJL is superior than those descriptors detected based on pixel intensity patterns such as ORB or SIFT is that it represents structure with physical existence, which is more robust to challenging scenarios. Moreover, its descriptor is distinctive and encodes the relationship between the two lines. Experiments on KITTI dataset show the effectiveness of the proposed method compared to loop detection using BoW trained with either point or line features.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
