<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gaussian Process | Jiang Muyun</title>
    <link>/tags/gaussian-process/</link>
      <atom:link href="/tags/gaussian-process/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Gaussian Process</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/images/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>Gaussian Process</title>
      <link>/tags/gaussian-process/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intelligent Soft Sensor Development for Nonlinear Industrial Big Data via Bagging Bayesian Gaussian Processes</title>
      <link>/publication/j-tie-svgpr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/j-tie-svgpr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    This paper is submitted and currently under review
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!-- Traditional Gaussian process regression (GPR) suffers from the cubic complexity and excessive computation burdens for industrial big data. To get rid of such defect, this work proposes a scalable soft sensor called bagging stochastic variational GP regression (BSVGPR). We first formulate the GP within the sparse and variational approximation framework. Then the stochastic variational inference (SVI) mechanism is induced, which can significantly break the formidable obstacle to nonlinear big data modeling. In addition, the imposed automatic relevance determination strategy will also leverage model interpretability with relevant feature weighting.  Based on that, the bagging mechanism is encompassed by combining a set of distributed predictors to form a powerful ensemble model. As the results, prediction accuracy is enhanced, while the stability is also well guaranteed. Both SVI and bagging allow for the parallel deployment. Therefore, a distributed diagram is developed for modeling and inference so that the BSVGPR can explore big data effectively and efficiently. For case study demonstrations, the proposed method is first evaluated on the numerical example, and then applied on the real-time oxygen prediction of hydrogen manufacturing unit. --&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
